Robert Z. Hancock 741 N. Entrada St. Chandler, AZ 85226

Phone: (480) 688-2860

Email: rzhancock@gmail.com
Website: robert.hancock7.com

SUMMARY

Technical Support Professional with 5+ years of experience in customer-facing positions supporting a wide range of websites and web-based products. Familiar with using and troubleshooting most common web design technologies and applications including HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript and WordPress as well as server-side technology such as a LAMP stack (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP), SSH, FTP, etc. Proven ability to quickly learn new software and procedures.

EXPERIENCE

Omnis Network, LLC

Technical Support Representative, May 2013 - Present

- Consult with customers to determine individual website needs.
- Assist with configuring web hosting, DNS and apps required by customer.
- Advise and assist with modifying website content and layout.
- Troubleshoot website errors and server connectivity issues.
- Educated end users on configuring and using email clients and web-based email.

Direct Marketing Media

Supervisor, August 2012 - February 2013

- Promoted to supervisor after first week of training in startup call center.
- Supervised customer retention and sales team.
- Trained new team members to use CRM.
- Assisted with call takeovers and de-escalation when necessary.
- Met one-on-one with team members on weekly basis to review metrics and determine areas of improvement.
- Provided reports and feedback to upper management.

GoDaddy.com, Inc.

Multiple Support Positions, September 2009 - March 2012

• Similar duties as Omnis Network but for a larger number of products and with greater focus on consultation and sales.

• Required to update knowledge of internal tools, products and services that changed frequently.

EDUCATION

Red Mountain High School, Mesa, Arizona High School Diploma, May 2006

Mesa Community College

Relevant courses: Linux Operating System and Linux System Administration.

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Troubleshooting and Debugging
- Collaboration and Communication